telebisyon.net 2011-10-07

# Privacy Policy

| Related  
---  
  
  * Universal Anti-Spam Policy
  * Terms of Service

Search  
---  
|   
---  
 | 

Telebisyon.net knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. **By visiting Telebisyon.net, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

**What Personal Information About Users Does Telebisyon.net Gather?**

The information we learn from users helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at Telebisyon.net. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us** : We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future browsing for you, improving our site, and communicating with you.
  *  **Automatic Information** : We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Telebisyon.net. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at Telebisyon.net if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist. 
  * **E-mail Communications** : To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Telebisyon.net if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our user list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our users.
  *  **Information from Other Sources** : For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better movie recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next communication more easily.

 **What About Cookies?**

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as Watched Episodes, My Schedule, and browsing preferences. 
  * The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Telebisyon.net's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

**Does Telebisyon.net Share the Information It Receives?**

Information about our users is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. Thus, for example, Telebisyon.net does not sell, and will never sell, information about you to external marketers, list brokers, or other third parties without user consent. Nor will we give such information to affiliated businesses or companies that we team up with to provide co-branded or jointly owned offerings unless you choose to take advantage of those offerings, and even then, any sharing of information is limited to information relating to the offering. Further, whenever we deal with user information, we will always comply with applicable laws and regulations in doing so.

 **What About Third-Party Advertisers?**

Our site includes third-party advertising and links to other websites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party websites.

These third-party websites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our website directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the National Advertising Initiative offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"), including information about how to opt-out of their information collection.

Telebisyon.net may also display targeted advertising based on personal information about users. Although Telebisyon.net does not provide any personal information to advertisers, advertisers (including ad-serving companies) may assume that users who interact with or click on a targeted advertisement meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

 **How Secure Is Information About Me?**

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

 **What Choices and Access Do I Have?**

  * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to take advantage of such Telebisyon.net features as My Movies and local show times. 
  * You can add or update certain information, such as your e-mail address. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
  * The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you will not be able to login or set preferences from and to this website if you do not use cookies.

 **Children**

Telebisyon.net is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, you may not submit information about yourself to Telebisyon.net. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit Telebisyon.net, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms and Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Washington Our website changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms and Conditions of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.

Effective Date: February 27, 2008. Last Modified: February 27, 2008

|
